<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coming Soon</title>
    <link>172.18.145.78/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Coming Soon</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="172.18.145.78/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>172.18.145.78/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>172.18.145.78/about/</guid>
      <description>RTT is a type of hypnotherapy that allows you to get to the root cause of an issue rapidly, often only one session is needed. Hypnotherapy allows you to access your subconscious (your emotional) mind, where often before the age of 7 we have formed beliefs about ourselves and the world due to events that have occurred when we were only young. We may not be aware of these subconscious beliefs as an adult, but know that something is holding us back/limiting us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>172.18.145.78/testimonial/20191208/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>172.18.145.78/testimonial/20191208/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;ve suffered with tinnitus and poor hearing for years, and was sceptical that Rapid Transformation Therapy could help, but it really did. Dr Gibbons was reassuring throughout the session, and helped me—under hypnosis—come to and understanding of why I had specifically developed tinnitus. This was really suprising, but in that moment I knew that I could choose not have tinnitus any longer. The ringing has gone, and my hearing has improved markedly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>172.18.145.78/testimonial/20193011/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>172.18.145.78/testimonial/20193011/</guid>
      <description>Deep Relaxation is relaxing and reassuring. Dr Gibbons maintains a very professional manner throughout the session, she makes you feel calm and at ease. The consultation lasts for about an hour and a half, however the time flies by and when finished it’s amazing to realise how much time has passed so comfortably. Since my consultation I have noticed a huge increase in my energy and a lift in my mood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>